<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Adventours</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">home</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="logininwithpassword"><u>Login with password</u></string>
    <string name="loginwithfingerprint"><u>LOGIN WITH FINGERPRINT</u></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>
    <string name="my_iterinary_description">My Iterinary</string>
    <string name="settings_button_description">Settings Button</string>
    <string name="about_us_button_description">About Us Button</string>
    <string name="help_center_button_description">Help Center Button</string>
    <string name="rate_us_button_description">Rate Us Button</string>
    <string name="like">like</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition1">1. Acceptance of Terms - By using AdvenTours, you agree to comply with and be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use our app.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition2">2. Scope of Service - AdvenTours  provides a platform for users to book flights, hotels, and access travel information.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition3"> 3. We do not own or operate any travel services.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition4">4. User Registration - You must be at least 18 years old to use our app. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition5"> 5. Cancellation and Refunds - Cancellation policies and refund eligibility vary by service provider. Please review specific booking details for this information.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition6"> 6. Privacy and Data Collection - We collect user data as described in our Privacy Policy. By using our app, you consent to the collection and use of your data.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition7"> 7. Liability and Disclaimers - AdvenTours is not responsible for any issues that may arise during travel, including delays, cancellations, or accidents. We recommend travel insurance.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition8">8. User Conduct - Users must adhere to respectful and lawful conduct within our app. Harassment, fraud, or abusive behavior is strictly prohibited.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition9">9. Termination - We reserve the right to terminate or suspend user accounts for violations of these terms or any unlawful activities.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition10">10. Updates and Changes - We may update these terms from time to time, and users will be notified of any changes. Continued use of the app after changes constitutes acceptance of the revised terms.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition11">11. Jurisdiction and Dispute Resolution These terms are governed by the laws of [Your Jurisdiction]. Any disputes will be resolved through arbitration in accordance with [Arbitration Rules].</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition12"> 12. Contact Information - For questions or concerns, please contact us at inquiry@adventours.com.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condition13">13. Compliance with Regulations: Adventours complies with all applicable laws and regulations in the provision of its services.</string>
    <string name="image">photogallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tours_lists">tours_lists_activity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="aboutus1">Welcome to AdvenTours, your buddy to adventures. We are your map in exploring the beauty of Pangasinan. Here\'s a glimpse of who we are:</string>
    <string name="aboutus2">Our Story - AdvenTours started as our Capstone project founded in 2023 with a simple goal: to empower travelers like you to explore Pangasinan with ease. Most of the members of our team love to explore different places and most of the members wish to travel to Pangasinan. So we decided to create a travel application that helps tourists who want to explore Pangasinan like us.</string>
    <string name="aboutus3">Meet the Team - Our dedicated team of travel enthusiasts works tirelessly to bring you the best experiences. Get to know the members of the project behind the scenes who make it all happen.</string>
    <string name="aboutus4">Daguiso, Justine D.\nGonzales, Jhenzen Anne I.\nParan, John Angelo C.\nSoriano, Trixie L.\nVibiesca, Hanah Keene M.</string>
    <string name="aboutus5">Contact Us - We are here to assist you. If you have questions, suggestions, or need support, please dont hesitate to get in touch with us:</string>
    <string name="aboutus6">Email: [inquiry@adventour.com]</string>
    <string name="aboutus7">Privacy and Security - We take your privacy and security seriously. Learn more about our commitment to protecting your data.</string>
    <string name="aboutus8">Terms and Conditions - Read our terms of use to understand our policies and guidelines when using AdvenTours.</string>
    <string name="aboutus9">App Version - 1\nCurrent Version: 1</string>
    <string name="aboutus10">Vision for the Future - We are dedicated to enhancing your travel experiences. Stay tuned for exciting updates and new features as we continue to grow and evolve.Thank you for choosing AdvenTours for your adventures. Happy travels!</string>
    <string name="aboutus11">POLICIES AND GUIDELINES</string>
    <string name="aboutus12">Privacy Policy: At AdvenTours, we respect your privacy. By using our app, you agree to the outlined terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="aboutus13">Terms of Service: When using our app, you agree to follow these terms of service. They include guidelines on user conduct, account termination, and disclaimers. Violating these terms may result in the suspension of your account.</string>
    <string name="aboutus14">Booking Policy:\n• Cancellation and refund policies vary by service provider. Please review them before making a booking.\n• Booking fees may apply, and these will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation.</string>
    <string name="aboutus15">Content Posting Guidelines: \n• You can post reviews, photos, and comments about your travel experiences.\n• Be respectful and avoid offensive or harmful content.\n• We reserve the right to remove or moderate content that violates our guidelines.</string>
    <string name="aboutus16">Security Measures:\n• We employ encryption and other security measures to protect your data.\n• Keep your login credentials secure, and report any suspicious activity immediately.</string>
    <string name="aboutus17">Review and Rating Guidelines:\n• Honest and constructive reviews are encouraged.\n• Fake or malicious reviews are not allowed and will be removed.\n• Ratings should reflect your genuine experience with the service.</string>
    <string name="aboutus18">Community Standards:\n• Treat fellow travelers and service providers with respect.\n• Harassment, discrimination, or any form of offensive behavior will not be tolerated.</string>
    <string name="aboutus19">Booking and Reservation Guidelines:\n• Carefully review booking details, including dates, times, and locations.\n• Follow the specific instructions provided by the service provider.\n• Contact the service provider directly for any changes or special requests.</string>
    <string name="aboutus20">Cancellation and Change Policies:\n• Each service provider has its cancellation and change policies. Review them before making a reservation.\n• Cancellation fees may apply and will be clearly stated during the booking process.</string>
    <string name="aboutus21">Safety Tips:\n• Prioritize your safety during your travels, including following health guidelines and local customs.\n• Emergency contact information is available within the app.</string>
    <string name="aboutus22">Customer Support Contact:\n• Our customer support team is available to assist you. Contact us through the app for prompt assistance.</string>
    <string name="aboutus23">By using our app, you acknowledge and agree to abide by these policies and guidelines. We aim to provide a safe and enjoyable travel experience for all our users.</string>
    
    
</resources>